Yachika paul: Sir wait
Quanta Gupta: yes sir
Bhanupriya Sharma: sir is the tweepy link read only?
Yachika paul: Sir what URL v need to add
Bhanupriya Sharma: yes
Ekant Bagri: +1
Tanya Goel: +1
Amandeep Kaur: +1
Anshee Mongia: +1
Shreya Goel: +1
Riya Raj: +1
Sheetal sehrawat: Sir could you please allow participants to join ?
Shivani singh: sir can you speak louder l
kritika verma: do we need to install tweepy?
kritika verma: okay sir
Shristi Sain: yes sir
Anshee Mongia: javascript object
Ekant Bagri: object?
Bhanupriya Sharma: dictionary of the data we asked for
Shradha Narain: the data is parsed into a python dict
Tamanna Verma: json what we asked for
Tamanna Verma: data*
Tamanna Verma: in form of python dictionary
Amandeep Kaur: Link : https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HAm6ebHzOzZoENVf-KhpV909Sn7mIjsF/view?usp=sharing
Ekant Bagri: sir, can you tell that pip install statement for tweepy?
Bhanupriya Sharma: !pip install tweepy
Ekant Bagri: thenks!
Rishika Anand: yes sr
Priya Chaturvedi: Yes
Shreya Srivatsan: yes
sapna rai: Sir would you please tell the account creation part, once more,
Tanya Goel: Citizens for Ethics
Shreya Goel: This Tweet is unavailable. Why is it showing this error
Amandeep Kaur: Getting TweepError
Anshee Mongia: sir giving error
Anshee Mongia: 404
Shreya Goel: Okay
sapna rai: twitter
sapna rai: developers account
Priya Chaturvedi: Just do import tweepy as tweepy @Shreya
Anshee Mongia: sir isn't 404 client side error?
sapna rai: yes sir
Ekant Bagri: sir there's a name eror that 'api' is not defined
Ekant Bagri: error*
sapna rai: okay sir
sapna rai: got it
Priya Chaturvedi: @Ekant import tweepy as tweepy
Tanya Goel: Sir I'm not getting the url for the tweet
Ekant Bagri: okay
Anshee Mongia: yes sir done
Tanya Goel: Sir I'm not getting the url for the tweet
Rishika Anand: Alfredo Del Mazo
Anshee Mongia: manya jain
Shreya Srivatsan: qocot_mktg
Tanya Garg: yes sir.
Anshee Mongia: does it have something to do with our personal twitter acc?
Bhanupriya Sharma: one_tweet.keys('entities')
Tanya Garg: .keys('entities')
kritika verma: requests.get('entities')
Akshat Ayush: one_tweet['entities']
Avinash Tulasi: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1uXuUaq96Eg7SGP7GuFPKEHKs_wTiC3-M/view?usp=sharing
Avinash Tulasi: f = open('my_file', 'r+')
lines = [line for line inf.readlines()]
f.close()
Anshee Mongia: item?
Anshee Mongia: no sir i was saying for instead of one_tweet
Anshee Mongia: i got 3
Ekant Bagri: can you scroll up?
Ekant Bagri: yes sit
Tanya Goel: I got 13
Ekant Bagri: sir*
Shreya Srivatsan: I got hashtags in all but 2
Avinash Tulasi: https://developer.twitter.com/en/apps/
Shristi Sain: can we do all these things on spyder also ?
Ekant Bagri: sir your screen is not visible
Shreya Goel: It will be there in the right hand side where all the participants are shown
Yachika paul: Sir your screen is not visible
pooja gera: pin the presentation screen, it won't go away :)
Ekant Bagri: got it
Yachika paul: M still not able to see screen
pooja gera: right side m jakr pin krdo presentation vali
pooja gera: where all screens are there
Shristi Sain: sir can we do all these things on spyder also??
Yachika paul: Only sir's picture is there
pooja gambhir: Sir the presentation is not visible
Tanya Garg: just pin the sir's name
Tanya Garg: showing presentation with sir's name
Rishika Anand: yes sir
Yachika paul: I did bt still presentation is not there
pooja gambhir: ok yes sir done thanks
unnati chhabra: where all of the participants screen are visible vha pr jakr pin krdo
Tanya Garg: presentation(Avinash Tulasi)
Pin this user..
Yachika paul: Got it
unnati chhabra: or you can search in participants as well
Tanya Goel: Got it sir
Anshee Mongia: done
Anshee Mongia: like search for a particular id?
Shreya Srivatsan: done
Abhigya Verma: done
Tanya Goel: 38575 followers maximum
sapna rai: Sir how to load that file?
Tanya Goel: Yes sir
Tanya Garg: f = open('my_file', 'r+')
lines = [line for line inf.readlines()]
Ekant Bagri: sir, this all_user_ids=[] just didn't run
Ekant Bagri: showing no error tho
Anshee Mongia: 3610 max
Ekant Bagri: oh okay
Anshee Mongia: index()?
Shreya Srivatsan: 77604 max
Carrysen Blackie: 2369
Bhanupriya Sharma: sir it is becoming difficult to follow since I dont have the keys, to just code and get desirable ooutput
Rishika Anand: 6403
Priya Chaturvedi: 8279
Amandeep Kaur: 2008
Shreya Goel: 54888
Sheetal sehrawat: 9234
pooja gambhir: 29033
Yachika paul: Sir error on data =tweet. _json
Yachika paul: Object has no attributes
Bhanupriya Sharma: please scroll up so that I shall know where to write the code to open up that file
pooja gera: 20822
pooja gera: @yachika print(tweet['user']['followers_count'])
pooja gera: I did this
pooja gera: works :)
Avinash Tulasi: with open("file.txt", "w") as output:
output.write(str(values))
Sanchita Singh: 6123
sapna rai: Sir can u please tell the command to load the text file.
Avinash Tulasi: with open("file.txt", "w") as output:
output.write(str(values))
Yachika paul: Yeah thanks it worked
Avinash Tulasi: https://kite.com/python/answers/how-to-read-a-text-file-into-a-list-in-python
Ekant Bagri: sir, where's that result txt file tho?
pooja gera: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1uXuUaq96Eg7SGP7GuFPKEHKs_wTiC3-M/view
pooja gera: text file^
Avinash Tulasi: https://drive.google.com/file/d/1uXuUaq96Eg7SGP7GuFPKEHKs_wTiC3-M/view?usp=sharing
Ekant Bagri: cool
Anshee Mongia: search_results[all_user_ids.index('24342')]._json
Bhanupriya Sharma: FOR THE CODE: with open("results.txt", "w") as output:
output.write(str(values))
Bhanupriya Sharma: i get error
Bhanupriya Sharma: NameError Traceback (most recent call last)
in ()
5 with open("results.txt", "w") as output:
NameError: name 'values' is not defined
Anshee Mongia: yes
Avinash Tulasi: https://forms.gle/PbHeLjofYbEfg5pg7
Anshee Mongia: trying
Bhanupriya Sharma: Sir honestly aap kahaan pahaunch gye, code krte krte,I am just not able to follow
Bhanupriya Sharma: I'm sorry I'm just not ableto cope up... need help
Tanya Garg: okay
Shreya Goel: def get_user_with_max_followers(hashtag):
result_cursor = api.search(q= '#'+hashtag , count=20)
all_user_follow = []
for tweet in result_cursor:
data = tweet._json
all_user_follow.append(data['user']['followers_count'])
print(max(all_user_follow))
get_user_with_max_followers("#covid")
Anshee Mongia: sir doesn't person_info store the required data?
Bhanupriya Sharma: please send this funtion in the chat box for reference
Ekant Bagri: sir only if you can give an overview of this func again?
Bhanupriya Sharma: function*
Avinash Tulasi: https://forms.gle/PbHeLjofYbEfg5pg7
Priya Chaturvedi: Sir can you give just a superquick go through of this function?
Priya Chaturvedi: Alrighty!
Ekant Bagri: cool
Ekant Bagri: sir, can you pls share this notebook w us?
Ekant Bagri: the updated one